what's most discomforting for me about you all support of people like Kamala etc is that you
think that they're in charge and I think that's the part for me that's like so even with everything
that's going on you still think that they're in charge and so if if they're not in charge then
what's the point of them being there why is that supportive or helpful to you no it's not helpful
because if they're not going to go in there and try and shake things up then they're just being used
to advance the agenda they are following the will of a greater force that greater force knows that
you know it's going to require little pittances to be given to the people to keep them placid or
whatever but they're never going to give you what you need give us what we need that's why there's a
fake scarcity happening on the planet at now at present we have to evolve beyond what we have
been told once we realize that those who are telling us are doing so for deleterious reasons
we know that mainstream media is lying we know that we have been trained by mainstream media
we know that when john d rockefeller put all this money into the general education board in the early
1900s in the united states he had no interest in actually creating a nation of intellects
like he literally said i don't want a nation of thinkers i want a nation of workers
and then reagan came in and said yeah so we about to keep that going and make america great again
by making college expensive and his head of education said we cannot have an informed proletariat aka an
informed working class once we know these things we have an opportunity to see them as inspiring versus
as demoralizing and i know that it's like really annoying sometimes to have me yelling them at you
but it's because i'm trying to get it through the indoctrination i'm trying to get it over
permeating under around sorry jedi the indoctrination she jumped off because she's already heard all this
before and she's like oh my god she's at it again yes she didn't go far though
thank you
i love you